let questions = [
    {
        numb: 0,
        question: "Ready to take the quiz again?",
        answer: "YES, I AM READY!",
        options: [
            "YES, I AM READY!",
            "NO",
            "yes",
            "no :("
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "A student is using a microscope to see if there's any bacteria in his blood. What action does the student perform when adjusting the magnification power of the objective lenses?",
        answer: "B) Rotating the revolving nosepiece",
        options: [
            "A) Rotating the stage",
            "B) Rotating the revolving nosepiece",
            "C) Adjusting the diaphragm",
            "D) Turning the fine adjustment knob" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2, 
        question: "An optical microscope utilizes visible light to form an image. What is the primary function of the glass lenses in this microscope?",
        answer: "C) Magnify and resolve images",
        options: [
            "A) Enhance the color of the specimen",
            "B) Adjust the contrast of the image",
            "C) Magnify and resolve images",
            "D) Provide illumination for the specimen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Galileo Galilei, in 1625, contributed to the development of microscopes by inventing one of the first compound microscopes. What additional feature did he introduce to enhance the functionality of his microscope?",
        answer: "D) Focusing device",
        options: [
            "A) Mechanical stage",
            "B) Eyepiece magnification",
            "C) Built-in light source",
            "D) Focusing device"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Hans and Zacharias Janssen, Dutch eyeglass makers, made a significant contribution to microscopy in the 1590s. What was the key innovation that led to the creation of the first compound microscope?",
        answer: "C) Experimenting with combinations of lenses in a small tube",
        options: [
            "A) Inventing the first lens",
            "B) Developing a method for lens polishing",
            "C) Experimenting with combinations of lenses in a small cube",
            "D) Designing a microscope with a built-in light source"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "As a part of their presentation on the historical evolution of microscopes, Justine seeks to understand the etymological roots of the term microscope. What is the origin of the word microscope?",
        answer: "C) Micros, meaning small, and skopein, meaning to look",
        options: [
            "A) Micros, meaning large, and skopein, meaning to observe",
            "B) Macro, meaning small, and skopein, meaning to magnify",
            "C) Micros, meaning small, and skopein, meaning to look",
            "D) Magni, meaning tiny, and ocular, meaning to examine"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6, 
        question: "A biology class is conducting an experiment to observe plant cells in various stages of mitosis. The teacher wants to switch between different objective lenses quickly. What part of the microscope facilitates this change?",
        answer: "D) Nosepiece",
        options: [
            "A) Diaphragm",
            "B) Stage",
            "C) Fine adjustment knob",
            "D) Nosepiece"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "A scientist is studying a microscopic organism and needs to examine its internal structures in detail. Which type of microscope would be most suitable for this task?",
        answer: "A) Transmission electron microscope", 
        options: [
            "A) Transimisson electron microscope",
            "B) Digital microscope",
            "C) Compound microscope",
            "D) Scanning electron microscope"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "A researcher is conducting a study to explore the internal structures of cells at a microscopic level. Which scientific field aligns with this specific investigation?",
        answer: "B) Microscopy",
        options: [
            "A) Virology",
            "B) Microscopy",
            "C) Icthyology",
            "D) Paleobotany"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "A student is setting up a microscope to observe a specimen under low magnification. What part of the microscope should the student adjust to control the amount of light passing through the specimen?",
        answer: "B) Diaphragm",
        options: [
            "A) Objective lens",
            "B) Diaphragm",
            "C) Eyepiece",
            "D) Stage"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Kylie, a biology student is preparing a presentation on cellular anatomy and needs to show detailed images of organelles. What type of microscope should Kylie recommend for obtaining high-resolution images of cellular structures?",
        answer: "C) Transmission electron microscope",
        options: [
            "A) Atomic force microscope",
            "B) Scanning electron microscope",
            "c) Transmission electron microscope",
            "D) Fluorescence microscope"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11, 
        question: "A researcher is studying the external features of a specimen and requires a microscope that can magnify the object 100x while providing a three-dimensional image. Which type of microscope should the researcher use for this study?",
        answer: "D) Stereomicroscope",
        options:[
            "A) Atomic force microscope",
            "B) Optical microscope",
            "C) Scanning electron microscope",
            "D) Stereomicroscope"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "A researcher is planning to study small biological specimens and needs a microscope that forms images using visible light. Which type of microscope should the researcher choose for this study?",
        answer: "D) Optical microscope",
        options: [
            "A) Scanning electron microscope",
            "B) Fluorescence microscope",
            "C) Transmission electron microscope",
            "D) Optical microscope"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "A student is setting up a microscope for a practical session and wants to place the specimen for observation. What part of the microscope should the student use for holding the specimen?",
        answer: "B) Stage",
        options: [
            "A) Eyepiece adjustment",
            "B) Stage",
            "C) Body tube",
            "D) Condenser lens"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "A researcher is using a microscope with oil-immersion objectives to examine a specimen in detail. What feature of the microscope should the researcher primarily utilize to achieve optimal focus in this situation?",
        answer: "A) Fine adjustment",
        options: [
            "A) Fine adjustment",
            "B) Zoom control",
            "C) Coarse adjustment",
            "D) Changing eyepieces"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "A student is studying microscopy and wants to understand the concept of resolution. What accurately represents the definition of resolution in microscopy?",
        answer: "D) Capacity to distinguish finer details",
        options: [
            "A) Illumination brightness",
            "B) Duration of microscope",
            "C) Magnification Capability",
            "D) Capacity to distinguish finer details"
        ]
    }
    ]